Welcome to Tetris! 

To be able to successfully play, please install the Graphics module by running "opam install graphics" on terminal. In order to do so, please make sure you have XQuartz also downloaded and working. 

After downloading the files and navigating into the directory, run "make build" and then "make play". The block on the screen can be moved left or right using the 'a' and 'd' keys, respectively. The block can be rotated clockwise using the 'w' key. The block can be automatically dropped using the spacebar. The game can be quit by pressing the key 'q'.
